Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
Look carefully with your heart
The truth lies far beyond
Hey you good or bad, truth or lies
Can't escape this gray smoke of the soul.
带上你的所有勇敢
Maybe that's how we can save this world.
Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
Mojo Spy
On the eve of the Firecracker Festival, Dorothy's Fortunate Egg robot
turned Boss Feng's Grain and Oil Shop into a popcorn shop.
But Boss Feng accused Firecracker Long, her old nemesis, of doing it all.
The conflict between them kept escalating.
Heart Ore
Excuse me, excuse me!
Wait for me!
Popcorn all over the ground!
Excuse me.
这里需要侦探吗？
We need it!
You're the one who did it!
What? I did that?
I said it wasn't me!
You still won't admit it?
You're so heartless.
Still trying to deny it?
It was you who did it
Stop pretending
Who's pretending?
Cut the act
I'm not acting!
It's you!
Are you still trying to deny it?
Look at this
Look what you've done to my shop!
So that's what happened
Everything in my shop
has all turned into popcorn
Thankfully, this fortune-bringing
Firecracker Festival Fortunate Egg is still fine
I'll keep it safe forever
Maybe it'll ward off the bad luck
someone has brought me
But what does that have to do with me?
Even if it wasn't you
Don't you have any sympathy?
You say *I* have no sympathy?
I was the first one who ran in here to save you!
You're so ungrateful!
Who are you calling ungrateful?
Say that again!
What did I say wrong?
Say that again.
I was the first one to run in and save you.
I can't hear you clearly.
You heartless thing!
The first to run in and save you
Your sympathy really makes me sick
It really is here after all.
You make me sad—you've got no heart.
You've really chilled my heart.
Jerk!
Love
Dreams
I never would have thought...
Thy-thy has slipped up twice, too.
Such a simple thing, made so complicated.
How dare you call her Thy-thy?!
Oh, what a surprise!
I know this was definitely an accident.
If Lord Dorothy makes a move again
It's sure to succeed.
Lord Eye
My charm is my promise.
Tomorrow night.
Tomorrow night, we'll pull it off.
Very good.
Dear viewers
Late last night.
Another transformation at the Grain and Oil Shop.
But this time it wasn't popcorn.
It was a grand fireworks show.
Don't cry.
Did you do this?
Yes.
No.
You're way out of line!
A grown man
How could you bully a weak woman like this?
How could you do this?
I'm innocent!
So many Fortunate Eggs!
Could it really be Firecracker Long?
I'm innocent! Innocent of what?
Suddenly there were lots of Fortunate Eggs.
So many, so many.
I really am innocent!
I'm innocent!
So many Fortunate Eggs!
So many, so many Fortunate Eggs!
Then they suddenly exploded!
I'm innocent!
Fortunate Eggs! That's it!
Boss Feng's beloved Firecracker Festival Fortunate Egg is gone.
Something's off here.
Looks like we should contact Hawxing.
Contact him?
No way.
Firecracker Festival Fortunate Egg.
Did you hear something?
No, nothing.
It's a signal from this egg.
The Fortunate Egg is sending a signal?
This egg could be the breakthrough.
Help!
Firecracker Long?
The truth is out.
I've been released.
Let's get you out of here.
Wait.
My Feng.
Long, darling.
This is...
I've been keeping it all along.
This is the wedding gift you gave me.
The Love Ore.
This really is the Love Ore.
This is a family heirloom.
Then why is it with Grain Feng?
Because she's my wife.
Back then, she wanted to open a grain and oil shop.
I wanted to open a firecracker shop.
So we had a falling out.
Thank you for saving me.
I'll pass this ore on to you.
Actually, that day I wanted to give you a bundle of fireworks.
To cheer you up.
But I never expected...
I know.
Let's make up.
Then you have to promise me one condition.
What condition?
You have to make me popcorn every day.
Okay, okay!
Yay! Yay! Yay!
Saying goodbye to today always makes us feel lost.
Look at tomorrow, waving to me from the horizon.
Every day, sunrise to sunset, time spins, and we dream of more.
Looking forward to every second, every moment of life.
My bright eyes are sparkling.
A smile that greets the sun.
Stepping quietly at the screaming crossroads.